Our camp is just up ahead.
Take a right at that
intersection and we're there.
Slow down, slow down.
It's right up ahead.
This is my place.
Mom!
Chengren!
Your leg!
How did this happen?
It hurts so bad.
Quick, get inside.
Hurry!
"The Last Oath"
(Episode 7: Class A Infected)
Ever since your dad died,
it's just been the two of us.
If anything were to happen to you,
what would I do?
We have no food,
and no medicine.
We can't stay in this dump
for much longer.
And now you're hurt.
Mom,
please stop crying.
It's all my fault.
It's my fault for being useless.
I couldn't catch any game,
and I even got myself hurt.
I'm just a burden to you.
Ma'am.
Please don't cry.
We injured him by accident.
We'll take full responsibility.
We'll stay here for a while.
The situation here...
you've seen it yourselves.
If you just leave us be,
a widow and her son,
we really won't survive.
Don't worry.
We'll go out and find some food tomorrow.
It's too late today.
We have some crackers in our bag.
Have some to hold you over.
How long have you lived here?
Are there any zombies nearby?
It's been a while.
Ever since we got here,
we haven't seen a single zombie.
It's very safe here.
Come with me.
We don't have much space.
We can make a bed for one of you here.
But it needs some tidying up.
There's a small shed outside.
The other can sleep there.
Right here.
Then he can...
He'll sleep with me.
It's fine, ma'am.
This will do.
Get some rest.
Don't worry about us.
It shouldn't take too long.
I feel like we can leave
in a couple of days.
No rush.
You're actually not in a hurry to leave?
You saw the boat, right?
We'll check on it tomorrow.
Once it's fixed, we'll take the waterway.
You're not sleeping yet?
You go ahead.
Heading out?
Don't worry, ma'am.
We'll be back with food.
The hull is mostly intact.
The gas tank is empty.
And the wiring is shot.
If we can find some wires and diesel,
we should be able to fix it.
Then let's get looking.
Still hungry?
I'm not stupid.
Last time was a total accident.
If you don't look for trouble,
there won't be any accidents.
Mount Zhiliao.
This waterway leads back to our old camp.
How are things on your end?
I found some usable wires.
Then we're all set.
Let's go.
You're back.
It must have been a long day out there.
I just made some soup.
With some wild greens I picked outside.
Have a sip.
Quench your thirst.
I'm not thirsty.
Neither of us is thirsty.
Ma'am,
you guys have it.
My mom spent ages cooking this.
If you won't drink it,
then I will.
We brought back quite a bit of stuff.
You guys are amazing.
So much good food!
Let's split it down the middle.
My son's leg...
I don't know when
it'll fully heal.
He can't work,
and he's just a burden.
And an old woman like me
is useless too.
To make some soup,
I could only find some
wild greens.
Just take it for now.
We can always find more later.
Thank you.
Thank you, young man.
You're both good people.
Eat up, eat up.
Hurry and eat.
What's the problem?
The fuel line is clogged.
Is it an easy fix?
It's not hard.
Just time-consuming.
Come on, let's head to the east woods.
I still need to clear the fuel line.
I plan on leaving tomorrow.
We need to stock up on food.
Tomorrow?
Then we should fix the boat ASAP.
Tell you what,
you go hunt, and I'll keep fixing it.
No way.
We go together.
Why?
You can hunt just fine on your own.
And you can't help with the boat anyway.
You want to leave as soon as possible,
but you refuse to split up the work.
What exactly do you want?
I can't leave you alone.
It's dangerous here.
Dangerous?
A-Leh,
just because I'm going with you
doesn't mean I'm your prisoner.
Me fixing the boat here
is just to help you out.
We don't have much time.
Let's not waste it keeping
tabs on each other.
You're back.
That's a really fat chicken.
Look, a chicken!
You're heading out again?
What took you so long?
What?
Afraid I'd run off?
Ma'am,
we're having chicken tonight...!
Your friend is really something.
It's been ages since we had meat.
Your hands are dirty. Go wash them first.